{"showBridgeTasks":true,"taskHeader":"Elevation Certification Services","__cache./api/resource/task/interview/62409/":{"taskOID":62409,"originalTaskOID":62409,"setID":8913,"interviewType":"TASK_INTERVIEW","questions":[{"questionID":503113,"questionDisplayText":"What is the purpose of the certification?","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"What is the purpose of the certification?","shortQuestionText":"What is the purpose of the certification?","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":true,"answers":[{"answerID":203992,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"For flood insurance","answerDisplayText":"For flood insurance","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":203993,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"For rebuilding or remodeling after a flood to prevent future damage","answerDisplayText":"For rebuilding or remodeling after a flood to prevent future damage","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":203994,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"For FEMA to be removed from a mandatory flood insurance requirement","answerDisplayText":"For FEMA to be removed from a mandatory flood insurance requirement","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4444,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Other","answerDisplayText":"Other","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":7136,"questionDisplayText":"Other Services Selected","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":2,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"Select any other services you would like.","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":1093,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Boundary survey (American Land Title Association)","answerDisplayText":"Boundary survey (American Land Title Association)","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6434,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Topographic or site map survey","answerDisplayText":"Topographic or site map survey","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4737,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Plot survey (subdivision/boundary alteration plots)","answerDisplayText":"Plot survey (subdivision/boundary alteration plots)","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1600,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Construction survey","answerDisplayText":"Construction survey","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4271,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"None","answerDisplayText":"None","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":90000,"questionDisplayText":"Request Stage","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Choose the appropriate status for this project:","shortQuestionText":"Project Status:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":5052,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Ready to Hire","answerDisplayText":"Ready to Hire","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4702,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","answerDisplayText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":80000,"questionDisplayText":"Desired Completion Date","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":3,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"When would you like this request to be completed?","shortQuestionText":"To be completed in:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":11149,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Timing is flexible","answerDisplayText":"Timing is flexible","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11150,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Within 1 week","answerDisplayText":"Within 1 week","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11151,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"1 - 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"1 - 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11152,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"More than 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"More than 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":7735,"questionDisplayText":"What kind of location is this?","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":4,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"What kind of location is this?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":20767,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Home/Residence","answerDisplayText":"Home/Residence","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":20766,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Business","answerDisplayText":"Business","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]}],"questionElements":[{"questionID":503113,"questionDisplayText":"What is the purpose of the certification?","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"What is the purpose of the certification?","shortQuestionText":"What is the purpose of the certification?","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":true,"answers":[{"answerID":203992,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"For flood insurance","answerDisplayText":"For flood insurance","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":203993,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"For rebuilding or remodeling after a flood to prevent future damage","answerDisplayText":"For rebuilding or remodeling after a flood to prevent future damage","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":203994,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"For FEMA to be removed from a mandatory flood insurance requirement","answerDisplayText":"For FEMA to be removed from a mandatory flood insurance requirement","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4444,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Other","answerDisplayText":"Other","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":203992,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"For flood insurance","answerDisplayText":"For flood insurance","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":203993,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"For rebuilding or remodeling after a flood to prevent future damage","answerDisplayText":"For rebuilding or remodeling after a flood to prevent future damage","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":203994,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"For FEMA to be removed from a mandatory flood insurance requirement","answerDisplayText":"For FEMA to be removed from a mandatory flood insurance requirement","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4444,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Other","answerDisplayText":"Other","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":7136,"questionDisplayText":"Other Services Selected","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":2,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"Select any other services you would like.","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":1093,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Boundary survey (American Land Title Association)","answerDisplayText":"Boundary survey (American Land Title Association)","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6434,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Topographic or site map survey","answerDisplayText":"Topographic or site map survey","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4737,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Plot survey (subdivision/boundary alteration plots)","answerDisplayText":"Plot survey (subdivision/boundary alteration plots)","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1600,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Construction survey","answerDisplayText":"Construction survey","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4271,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"None","answerDisplayText":"None","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":1093,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Boundary survey (American Land Title Association)","answerDisplayText":"Boundary survey (American Land Title Association)","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6434,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Topographic or site map survey","answerDisplayText":"Topographic or site map survey","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4737,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Plot survey (subdivision/boundary alteration plots)","answerDisplayText":"Plot survey (subdivision/boundary alteration plots)","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1600,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Construction survey","answerDisplayText":"Construction survey","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4271,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"None","answerDisplayText":"None","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":90000,"questionDisplayText":"Request Stage","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Choose the appropriate status for this project:","shortQuestionText":"Project Status:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":5052,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Ready to Hire","answerDisplayText":"Ready to Hire","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4702,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","answerDisplayText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":5052,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Ready to Hire","answerDisplayText":"Ready to Hire","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4702,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","answerDisplayText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":80000,"questionDisplayText":"Desired Completion Date","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":3,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"When would you like this request to be completed?","shortQuestionText":"To be completed in:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":11149,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Timing is flexible","answerDisplayText":"Timing is flexible","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11150,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Within 1 week","answerDisplayText":"Within 1 week","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11151,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"1 - 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"1 - 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11152,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"More than 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"More than 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":11149,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Timing is flexible","answerDisplayText":"Timing is flexible","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11150,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Within 1 week","answerDisplayText":"Within 1 week","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11151,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"1 - 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"1 - 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11152,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"More than 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"More than 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":7735,"questionDisplayText":"What kind of location is this?","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":4,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"What kind of location is this?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":20767,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Home/Residence","answerDisplayText":"Home/Residence","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":20766,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Business","answerDisplayText":"Business","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":20767,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Home/Residence","answerDisplayText":"Home/Residence","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":20766,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Business","answerDisplayText":"Business","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]}]},"categoryPerformanceTest":true,"scrollyPathPageBase":"","providedPostalCode":"","__cache./api/resource/task/62409/?r_version=1":{"taskOid":62409,"taskName":"Elevation Certification","taskDescription":"Obtain an Elevation Certificate","xmTaskDescriptor":"Elevation Certification Services","matchable":false,"profileable":false,"esScore":0.0,"defaultCostGuideTaskId":null,"active":true,"taskKeywords":"flood, fema, elevation, certificate, survey, surveyor","textMessagingName":"Elev. Cert.","rolloverLongDesc":"A FEMA Elevation Certificate is a document often requested by mortgage or title companies or flood insurance companies who want to determine the status of a building in relationship to the flood plain as it relates to the Flood Insurance Rate Map (FIRM). The information on the Elevation Certificate may be used to determine flood insurance rates for the client.","rolloverShortDesc":"Establish elevation a property or building in relation to flood plain.","sectorId":"HS","metaDescription":"Find local services that offer Flood Elevation Certification.  HomeAdvisor will connect you with prescreened and customer-rated surveyors in your area","htmlTitle":"FEMA and Flood Elevation Certification \u003ccity\u003e \u003cstatecode\u003e","contentDescription":null,"pwcId":5,"acceptGoal":3,"multiZip":false,"preMatchTypeId":5,"bridgeTaskOid":0,"bridgeTaskText":null,"bridgeTaskLinkText":null,"bridgeTaskLinkId":0,"bridgeTaskActive":"N","xmName":"Elevation Certification","redirectToTaskOid":-1,"spDisplayName":"Elevation Certificate","xmHeaderDescriptor":"Describe Your Elevation Certification Need","urlName":"Elevation-Certification","taskConsiderationId":3,"siteVisible":true,"attributeMatchable":true,"htmlTitleTloc":"\u003cspcount\u003e Best Flood Elevation Certification Companies in \u003ccity\u003e \u003cstatecode\u003e","searchKeywords":"flood, fema, elevation, certificate, survey, surveyor, land, property, flood plain","emcCategoryOid":-12005,"locationDisplayText":"What is the location of your project?","semLocationDisplayText":"To get started, enter the location of your project","commentsPromptText":"Please provide a short description of your project","primaryQuestionSetId":8913,"locationSpecific":false,"commercial":false,"viewFirstParentTask":false},"hideAllSemIcons":false,"scrolly_persistedParams":{},"addressId":null,"AdobeFlickerMgmtOn":false,"SCROLLY_FILTER_NON_REQUIRED_33367":false,"headerBranding":{"src":"/images/consumer/cobranding/HA.svg","name":"ha"},"entryPointId":0,"matchingSourceId":2,"scrollyProgressBarTest":false,"isMobile":false,"consumer":{"entityId":0},"affiliateCode":"sm_def_sto","twoPageSubmit":true,"sar":true,"scrolly_customDefaults":["50001_10002","8152_10002","30001_10002","160804_10002","20001_10002","160807_10002","160805_10002","502713_10002","160810_6938","8373_67562","8374_67566"],"entityId":0,"sessionId":"1564368210609pwspr010376737CC5AE756748174EA7F763C984D.pwspr010-1","shouldShowTasks":true,"KNOWN_USER_SCROLLY_TEST_SITE_33390":"ctrl","semThreeIcons":false,"isCookielessUser":true}